now I'm gonna be honest with you I think
putting myself on display in spawn was
probably not a good idea
um hopefully someone comes along was a
customer does anybody need anything
testing
hello
I'm ready
doc
hey dude
um hello what are you wearing I'm I'm a
guinea pig it's Green's guinea pig
Services I I'm I'll test anything for
six Diamonds the only bad thing is I've
been in this cage for two days now
nobody came by a lot I'm not even joking
I have literally been in this cage for
like two days
wait what so this is your shop here and
you're sitting up there all the time
wait what's what's going on okay you're
selling stuff too right okay Koreans you
lazy start traveling shop okay grindy
blocks
okay okay okay that's good but what else
what is this this is my this is my
services so I thought instead of just
selling blocks why not sell services to
people I think that some people need
stuff testing like your Phantom run but
that's already been done
um but it turns out people don't need
anything testing and I've been in this
cage for a long time waiting for a
customer
well good you have me man I'm gonna be
your customer I got something to test
it's about market research and you are
the perfect customers freedom
oh man that's good it's glorious
so look I'm addressing the professional
Minecraft player the pro that's me not
the noobs that's clearly you yeah that
is me so
all right one two three four five six
diamonds you said right so here's your
payment in advance that's how we conduct
business here at the NHO okay all right
so um yeah we need to head over to the
to the guardian farm and what do you
think about it it's what do you think
about it yeah it's good but does it have
a flaw do you think it's annoying if you
stand there and whack those Guardians by
hand right and you know then you take
damage slowly and then you have to eat
constantly right wouldn't it be great
if there would be an additional service
at the farm that makes all your farming
experience way better literally a
life-changing XP farming experience I'm
interested interesting all right from
now on you know in a good test
environment
um the tester remains silent and
observes the customer in his natural
habitat okay all right got it I'm not
here I'm not here so I'm here to use
this Guardian Farm
I've got some stuff
um well I've noticed that there's a
thing here NHO Beacon buff service
let's have a look does this book say
anything it does Welcome to the NHO
Beacon Boost service tired of grinding
uh do those pesky Guardians hurt you and
you're sick of constant eating and the
verge of death don't worry the NHO has
your back get an NHL Beacon boost season
pass for unlimited access to
Regeneration and resistance Beacon bus
while grinding 16 diamonds for a
life-changing experience literally a
dirt cheap isn't this already really
compelling right 16 diamonds dude that's
a lot
a lot that's a lot for a lifetime a
lifetime I haven't tested the product
yet can I go in yeah maybe you have to
yeah yeah maybe you have to experience
it first
all right there's no just toss the book
on the ground yeah
oh oh you got an achievement for that
even yeah I know I should charge you for
that yeah
all right so I got the pass and then I
gotta grind
yes now now feel the change feel the
change in experience okay just go to the
to the grinder right walk right up to it
all the way yes now
hit it
oh I want to see how you nicely
regenerate and it's way more pleasant to
be there
yeah I don't have to do anything
oh my God
so this is not worth 16 diamonds for you
man come on bro
oh
wait what I haven't talked to him yet I
mean you know technically I'm outside of
this property here
should I should I lower the price
um I'm a poor man on This Server hence
why I'm in this guinea pig suit
um so
well for you I mean there's a special
offer uh-huh
and tried it out now and I already paid
you six six diamonds you would you could
keep this past for free
but you know there's of course there's a
little little catch to it
would be very nice of you if you could
do some advertising for the service and
tell everybody about your life-changing
experience while you were grinding here
it's like a kind of a sponsorship deal I
give you the pairs for free and you
advertise the place of it I'm just I'm
just the guinea pig here I'm not a
marketing guy well let's say you hang
out with mambo he's your friend right
and then Mambo casually says man I need
to go grind some XP and then you could
say dude recently at the guardian Farm
dog installed this amazing thing and
grinding Expedia is the best ever right
there is that you know that's that's
easy no I guess I could mention it
but I'm not gonna go out my way so let's
say if I paid you
six more diamonds yeah I guess I guess I
could bring it up with a few people
so you can keep the book by the way it's
yours right it's it's like an eye trade
pass now
um I could give you another one you
could give that to another customer I
just think 16 diamonds is heavy
you're not you're not easy you're not
one an easy one to convince huh no I I
know I mean that like I I think for
people like me
it's it's too much I'd rather just eat
some more potatoes you know
don't you make much money on the pickle
shop no I thought it was a genius
business no I don't make any money on
the pickle shop that was a waste of time
all right what do you think I'm in this
suit man
if I made money from pickles I wouldn't
be dressing up like a guinea pig
it kills me man the shop killed me so it
was a partial success
I'm sorry about that maybe we shouldn't
argue about the prices you got it for
free yeah plus an additional book you
can give to a friend that is yeah that's
not my place to complain they can decide
whether it's expensive or not all right
good so I would say that was a
successful experiment I thank you very
much for your guinea pig Services thank
you much much much appreciated next time
when I pay you to test something please
give me a bit more positive feedback
especially about the pricing I pride
myself on my honest guinea pig Services
I'm an honest guinea pig and I won't
tell you just what you want to hear
okay yeah okay that makes sense I mean
you want to have valid feedback
constructive criticism exactly so you
say everything is good but I need to
consider maybe lowering the prices
potentially maybe eight eight
uh I'd say 10.
all right I'll keep it at 16. all right
I guess I'll go get back in my cage
that was a tidy little profit actually
so I guess we get back in here and then
wait for another customer
this is definitely not the most
efficient way but I'm having a lot of
fun so far that was easy money if you
ask me so let's just hop ourselves back
in and then we wait for another customer
actually while we're here let's head
into the shop
oh look at we're making money now
oh my goodness 42 diamonds in total from
today's Antics we've sold a lot of sand
and gravel
my goodness
that is excellent we need to we need to
save these hold on let's go and sleep
for the night
let's pop that in there oh we're back
above a stack of diamonds oh brilliant
all right well back in the cage we go
and one two
time to wait for another customer we're
making some profit today
this is an interesting looking shop
right who puts the signs at that sort of
angle that make them difficult to read I
don't know oh it's old grian is it you
lazy sod traveling Market by grindy
blocks at a cost I'm not interested in
uh and any grindy blocks but I heard
there's some sort of guinea pig service
going on over half the sign there
certainly is what young man
you're in a cage oh well I have been for
a couple of days now waiting for
customers do you need something testing
because I'll test it I I happen to have
a test and if that didn't sell it for
you I don't know what will to be honest
with you you've sold you've sold it I
I'm in need of your services I'm a
little bit concerned you've been hanging
out here for a couple of days I've seen
that you've been on the server I thought
you'd be busy digging or something like
that you know let me break you out that
would be the smart thing oh
see I saved you huh thank you from your
own design so six diamonds I'll test
anything it's a deal I happen to not
have my Ender Chest on me right now
therefore no can I give you the diamonds
after the experiment has been done uh
yeah sure and if you pay 10 diamonds
I'll throw in one of Doc's passes if you
want one of those
what is this a pass to it's a beacon
pass if you use the guardian farmer tool
for XP where did you get this it's a
done deal wait it's a copy no it's not
it's a real one
now is he says Coffee that there are
recipes he put all copies in there he
gave them to me I have the evidence
okay I'll take your word on it also I'd
like I need an explanation as to uh what
this little onesie you're wearing is
what do you mean I mean oh you know
you're literally a guinea pig I'm a
guinea pig what did you do you need me
to explain it's green skinny pictures it
just clicked in my mind a moment like
I'm slow like that you'll learn that I'm
slow if it was Green's chicken Services
I'd be dressed as a chicken are you
following me yeah right now now we want
to head all the way up to this glass box
but what I need you to do is land on top
of the glass box okay gotcha
excellent now this is a test of my
flying skills
my yeah oh when you land hold down shift
it helps you land on a block right
that's it so now what we need is just
night time okay so now we play the
waiting game I'm used to that sitting in
a cage waiting
so the Sun is setting over nothing
because we're that high up what is it
we're testing here
oh you'll soon find out all right and
what I will say is Don't Panic don't
jump off the edge oh I'm surprised you
haven't thrust it out already but uh
I'm just the guinea pig I I'm not
supposed to question or anything I'm
just yeah yeah you're just I'm just here
to test if you want I can perform a
little dance for you while we wait
don't scream dance
Guinea Pig dance
you know I would be impressed but it
needs a little bit of jumping in there
as well you know I've got to show off
all the moves maybe a little bit of uh
hand shuffling doing a little bit of
this
okay
that's interesting
they weren't supposed to attack you what
maybe they're mine
I slept recently you just you just
wanted me to die
no no I genuinely thought they weren't
going to attack you due to things that I
have previously test but it turns out
that they will attack another player
even though you've just slept in a bed
think of all the things you've just
taught your audience right there about
the Phantom you know
that was a good test you just wanted me
to die
dude I I so thought they weren't going
to attack me no you didn't because they
were my Phantoms
what was the idea that I could kill them
for you on top well actually I was gonna
troll you because I didn't expect them
to attack me then I was going to log out
and then they would have attacked you
but they didn't they just wait for me
anyway
it's yeah it's really weird because
they're my Phantoms I've spawned them in
and now they're targeting me but they
targeted you first instead
I feel cruel now I'm battered and I've
got no I've got no hunger whatsoever
like I've been thoroughly I've been
thoroughly guinea pigs in this
experiment yes and I can't give you the
diamonds either can I because uh the
experiment didn't work as I uh no I
should find you
one two three four five six
are you not gonna pay for the pass as
well I've trolling yeah
all right ten more diamonds for the bank
I'll tell you what I had no diamonds at
the start of today and I have made a
pretty sweet profit from that little car
experience and I think I'm probably done
staying in that cage now uh I don't
think it's gonna take a break from all
that yeah it's not a good use of my time
at all
um I might just be yeah I guess if
you've been waiting in there for a
couple of days that's you know you could
have mined more diamonds in that time
yeah well I thought I thought people
needed more things testing than they did
and you just used it as a way to kill me
so you know I thought it was going to be
more interesting than that unfortunately
those Phantoms went straight for you I'm
gonna retire from this guinea pig life I
think my guinea pig days are definitely
over so let's go and put these diamonds
away sit stacking a bit not too shabby
not too shabby at all but we should
definitely get back to some real work
and I guess oh I guess I'll put a sign
there there we go Green's guinea pig
service we'll test anything for six
diamonds if he's not in the cage send a
request and he will suit up I think
that's probably a good place to leave
Green's guinea pig testing facility
I can't help but feel that most people
just saw a way to to use me as best as
they could and not really have anything
proper to test Zoomer in particular did
not did not have a plan he did not
expect that to go that way he was
meaning to troll me but he accidentally
trolled me in a different way
oh well I really I really really like
this little shop I like the crane design
and I really like how this has come out
for something that was freestyled on the
spot I'm pretty happy with how this has
come out if you want me to make a more
detailed tutorial on how to make this
I'd be more than happy to plop one on
the channel it wouldn't take too long at
all okay so let's head back to the base
and get some real work done
mumbo's AFK again
oh no
it's hard to resist he doesn't see me
I was so gonna push him over the edge
he still didn't see me
oh I should have just done it I should
have just done it oh that would have
been so funny oh my goodness maybe next
time I like to just come and see what
mumbo's working on he's working on
Redstone stuff so I'm not that
interested it's not it's not as exciting
so I don't know what's going on it looks
too complicated for me it's like looking
at someone putting together a computer
I'm like don't know what's going on so
now it's time to just work on this
because I decided that this side is
better which means we've got to remove
this side and then actually complete
this all together and there are mob
spawning everywhere in here at the
moment so it's not safe at all so we're
gonna do a very quick and short time
lapse this actually took a really long
time so I deleted the smaller side and I
removed any alterations that I made to
this little bit of bass this was like
four or five hours of building and
collecting because of course I ran out
of concrete and then I had to go and
turn the powder into concrete itself so
that took time and and eventually I got
round but what took the most time was me
constantly making mistakes on this
little build as simple as it might look
at making a big circle if you mess up
just one block it means that it just no
longer comes into line and one quarter
might be different to another and it
might not be right all the way around so
it took a long time but eventually I did
correct everything and we got this
after that lovely time lapse I've
actually made a decent amount of
progress to the point where we have a
fully enclosed space for our first layer
and I even added this circle around the
Bottom now I've got a really really cool
plan for this and I guess I'll just
share it with you because I want to see
if you guys are on board with this so
I'm thinking inside here where my
conduit and stuff is I'm going to drain
that and I'm gonna actually use that as
a space now I'm thinking what I can do
because this was a bit of a mistake to
be honest but I'm not going to spend any
time getting rid of it so what I thought
is I'm going to basically replicate here
but a bigger circle around the edge so
this will go all the way down and
connect to the sea floor and then that
will create this like little double
glazed area between these two layers now
what I'm going to do is turn that into a
coral reef of some kind so it is a giant
cylindrical Aquarium barium and it's
going to be filled with tropical fish
and it's going to be tried to be as much
warm water as possible because obviously
we're in the deep ocean now I can just
imagine how cool it would be with some
really bright colors sand in between so
really stand out amongst the gravel and
then from the inside you have an
aquarium and from the outside it just
looks completely out of this world so
that's the vague plan for this area at
the moment and hopefully I can put trees
around the edge or have a walkway or
something and eventually we could go up
here to the top as well there's just a
lot of stuff that needs to be done and
we've got a long way to go actually now
I'm thinking that we cover this with
some cyan stained glass that way you can
see downwards into it as well as from
that angle and from the ocean itself but
I think this is something that's
probably gonna have to be another burner
in the background because I've got I've
also got a lot of other things including
this tweet this mysterious tweet from
Mumbo that I saw it says to go to the
shopping district and he's telling
everyone to tell me or and the other
Hermits to go and visit it now that is
enough to pique my interest if mumbo's
made something you know something's up
you know something special is going on
so yeah let's empty our inventory before
we go and have a look I don't think
Mumbo is the type of person to try and
kill other Hermits but you never know oh
I think I see it
okay I think that's it is it the sad why
is there a sad Mumbo
oh maybe he's not sad he looks really
sad and he's confused okay I'm I'm
intrigued let's get some diamonds and
check this out also it looks like our
armor stands have been put in how
awesome is this oh maybe we've got a
couple more also I actually put a uh
fence under here
no more sales that's really sad let's go
up and have a look at this Mumbo shop
this is going to be interesting
foreign
there doesn't seem to be anything here
there's no trickery no tomfoolery it's
just four chests
please read
oh goodness
congratulations you just bought a
spoiler I'm away in the Philippines
right now and this build hasn't been
uploaded yet normally this would be a
problem but not here as this is a
spoiler store as you are reading this
book it is clear you have shown spoilers
and thus you must pay for what you have
taken three diamonds must be deposited
in the chest immediately come back soon
uh
uh I feel like such a fool
there's no reason for this shop is there
now I've got to go and put three
diamonds in
what a joke what an absolute joke
I've bought a spoiler
this is unbelievable mumbo's charging me
for spoiling his video and there's
nothing to spoil except this this this
weird upset Mumbo thing
I guess we better follow the rules but
I'm not happy about this I'm not happy
about this at all
he's taking three of my hard-earned
diamonds away not impressed
I can't believe I'm paying for this
nonsense
right there it is three diamonds but I'm
also gonna put this in I want to refund
I want I want a refund of this because
this isn't cool I don't know how I'm
gonna get him back for this this is so
stupid this is like the stupidest thing
I've I've ever seen do you know what I
could have just like cut this out of the
video entirely but I was so happy to be
involved in something
that I did it anyway well I don't want
to lie to you guys but that was a pretty
disappointing to the end of this video I
can I can tell you that for nothing I
feel like I should warn other people
like I should leave a sign saying don't
do it guys it's a trap
but I don't want to be the only one that
fell for this I don't want to be the
only one I want I want at least three
other people they say there's only four
there so I want at least three other
people to to get this as well so I'm not
the only idiot that did it I mean look
at that tweet that is the Tweet of
someone that's definitely pulling a
prank I thought oh I don't know what I
expected but I didn't expect to have to
pay for something stupid like this
oh Mumbo he's actually off to the
Philippines which is why he did this
apparently he's uh I'm away in the
Philippines right now and I wish him all
the best I know that a huge amount of
people from the Philippines actually
watch it so shout out to you guys wish I
could go myself and I think that's it
for today's video we made so much
progress you guys are gonna be excited
when you see what I come up with for the
next bit so I'm gonna I'm gonna spend a
lot of time using all of the resources
that I have in my base to try and finish
this off as much as possible at least in
the lower level and then we're gonna do
the thing that I'm gonna regret a lot
which is converting this we're gonna
have to drain this and I know I'm gonna
regret it and how do I get out of here
I didn't think this through why did I oh
why did I make a hole let me out let me
out there we go well thank you very much
oh I love the fact that it's big enough
to fly in here well thank you very much
everyone for watching this video hope
you enjoyed it love to hear your
thoughts on the bass and the guinea pig
service and everything else that you've
seen on this series so far
good bye